ymultimedia.com 2010-12-04

# yMultimedia.com - The Next Generation in Affiliate Marketing - Privacy Policy

yMultimedia! LLC. ("yMultimedia!") has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering, use and dissemination practices solely for the web site on which this policy is placed by yMultimedia! via a hyperlink (the "Site"), and not to any other web site, product or service. By using or accessing the Site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE.**

**Collection of Personal Information**  
We do not collect personal information about Site users unless such information is voluntarily provided by the user. Our registration forms require consumers to provide certain contact information such as name, email address, telephone number, mobile number, physical address and other personal information. 

**Use of Personal Information and sharing with Third Parties**

Many of our services involve the collection of personal information which is in turn provided or sold to third parties to contact you directly regarding their products and services. Therefore, you should carefully read our information disclosure practices below and consider whether or not you want to provide such information. 

The personal information voluntarily provided by users is used and shared as described in this policy, including to: 

  1. provide you with the services or products you have requested from us, 
  2. send you promotional offers for various products and services via direct mail, telemarketing, SMS text messaging and email or
  3. provide your personal information to third parties whom we feel may have products or services that may be of interest to you, and who in turn may contact you via direct mail, telemarketing, SMS text messaging and email either themselves or through their affiliates or customers. We may use vendors and contractors to provide our services. Therefore, such vendors and contractors may be provided with your personal information, but they are only allowed to use such personal information in connection with the services they provide to the Site.

Certain offers are provided by third parties. **If you provide your personal information for certain offers, we may give your personal information to such third parties for them to contact you directly.** After the information is given to such third parties, those parties will use the information pursuant to their own privacy practices and yMultimedia! is not responsible for, or able to control, such practices. Therefore, if you do not want your personal information used in this manner, you should not provide it to yMultimedia! in the first place. 

Consumers who opt-in to receive offers or voluntarily provide their personal information to yMultimedia! may receive emails, telephone calls or direct mail from yMultimedia! or our partners with whom we share personal information. 

If you do not want to receive offers from yMultimedia! or its partners, then you should not provide personal information in connection with any offers on the Site. In addition, you may opt-out of receiving certain future communications from us (but not third parties who have been provided with your personal information as explained in this policy) by following the instructions in the Choice/Opt-Out section below. 

We may also obtain information about you from third parties and use that information to enhance the information that we already have about you. For instance, if we just have your name and email address, we may use a third party to obtain your telephone number and physical address. All of the combined information will be used in accordance with this policy. 

Please note that we reserve the right to access and/or disclose personal information and non-personal information we gather as required by courts or administrative agencies and to the extent required to permit us to investigate suspected fraud, harassment or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, a web site’s terms, or the rights of third parties or to investigate any suspected conduct which we deem improper. We may also disclose and/or transfer your personal information in connection with a sale, merger or reorganization of all or a part of Intermark. 

**Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information**  
We may collect non-personal information (or aggregate information) during your use of our Site, including IP address, pages viewed, click-stream data and browsing habits. Non-personal information may be shared with third parties who are not affiliated with yMultimedia!. 

Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your session and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use (and our third party advertisers and business partners may use) cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. We also use cookies once a form is submitted as an indicator that the form was filled. "Cookies" are pieces of information that may be placed on your computer by a web site for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with that web site. Many web sites use cookies for these purposes. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use our Site, but it may interfere with some of its functionality. yMultimedia! does not use cookies to automatically retrieve personal information from your computer without your knowledge. 

In addition to cookies, we may also use (and our third party advertisers and business partners may use) clear gifs or web beacons to improve the performance of the Site, provide certain features such as advertising or to anonymously track usage of the Site. Clear gifs / web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, which operate much like a cookie, and are used to track the online activity of Site users. In addition, we may use such devices in our HTML-based emails to track the usage of such emails in much the same manner as usage of the Site is tracked. These devices are not used by yMultimedia! to automatically collect person information. 

**Security**  
This Site has reasonable security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of personal information under our control. However, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications will be free from unauthorized access by third parties such as hackers and your use of the Site demonstrates your assumption of this risk. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
To opt-out of any mailings from yMultimedia!, you may follow the opt-out procedures set forth in our emails to you or send an email to us at [optout@ymultimedia.com](mailto:optout@ymultimedia.com)

If you do not wish us to share your personal information with third parties who may use such information for direct marketing purposes, you may send an email to us at [removepersonalinfo@ymultimedia.com](mailto:removepersonalinfo@ymultimedia.com). 

However, we are not responsible for removing your personal information from the lists of any third party who has previously been provided your information in accordance with this policy. You will need to contact such third parties directly, review their privacy policies or respond to their messages sent to you and request to opt-out. 

All opt-out requests sent to us to opt-out of future correspondence or use of personal information by us will be process as soon as possible, though you may continue to receive messages from us and we may continue to share your personal information until such request is processed. 

**Correct/Update**  
To change and modify information previously provided to yMultimedia!, you may email us at [update@ymultimedia.com](mailto:update@ymultimedia.com)

**Links**  
This Site contains links to other sites. yMultimedia! is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. Please read the privacy policies of these linked sites, because their privacy practices may differ from ours. 

**Protection for Children**  
We have no intention of collecting personal information from children under the age of 13. When we become aware that personal information from a child under 13 has been collected without such child’s parent or guardian’s consent, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time by posting such changes on this page. You should check this page frequently to see if there have been any changes. However, if at any time in the future we plan to use personal information in a way that differs from this policy, we will post such changes here and provide you the opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes. 

**Terms of Use**  
Use of this Site is governed by, and subject to, the legal notices contained in our Terms of Use, Terms and Conditions or similar policies set forth on the Site. Your use, or access, of the Site constitutes your agreement to be bound by these provisions. **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE PROVISIONS YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE.**

**USA**  
Our Site is maintained in the United States of America. By using the Site, you freely and specifically give us your consent to export your personal information to the USA and to store and use it in the USA as specified in this policy. The laws of the State of New York, USA shall apply to all collection and use of information in connection with this Site. 

**Effective Date**  
This privacy policy was last updated on June 12, 2009. 

**Contacting yMultimedia**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact: 

yMultimedia! LLC  
1041 Market Street #191  
San Diego, Ca 92101
